Joel Reyes

UX/UI Designer/Graphic Designer

City: Los Angeles, CA 90044 Email: joelreyes174@gmail.com

Phone:(323)675-8303 Website: joelreyes.xyz

Professional Summary

I am a UX/UI Designer with a desire to make my designs into a reality. I am highly motivated and have a strong drive to enhance my skills and contribute to user-focused experiences. My emphasis is on developing designs that cultivate confidence and ensure user satisfaction.

SKILLS

- Fluent in English and Spanish
- Visual Design, User Research, Information Architecture
- Mockups, Wireframing, and prototyping
- Graphic Design
- Web development (HTML & CSS)
- Figma
- Adobe Cloud
 - Photoshop
 - Illustrator
 - Indesign
- Blender 3D
 - Modeling
 - Animation
 - Compositing
- Microsoft office
 - Words
 - Excel
 - Powerpoint

EDUCATION

UX/UI Certificate - Cal State Long Beach

February 2022 - December 2022

HTML, CSS, JS Web Development - Coursera Online Certificate

January 2023 - May 2023

Studio Art Associate's Degree - El Camino College

January 2020 - November 2022

EXPERIENCE

MV Coffee Roasters - Freelance UX/UI/Web Developer

August 2023 - Present

- Developed a Brand Guide including Brand Name, Mission Statement, Logo, Color palette, and typography.
- Designed key UX deliverables such as user personas, user flows, and a detailed site map to inform navigation and layout.
- Created high-fidelity visual assets, including:
 - Website Design
 - Packing Design (coffee bags, coffee box)
 - o Business Cards
 - Product Labels
- Developed on-page SEO strategies to improve search visibility and user engagement.

See case study for more information

Website: https://www.mvcoffeeroasters.com/password

Password: iLikeCafe_alatte3

Chrishaunda Lee Perez Website - Freelance Web Developer

July 2024 - August 2024

- Developed a Brand guide that focused on a cohesive Color palette, and typography.
- Designed and delivered key visual assets to support the brand's online presence.
- Created a fully responsive, User-centered Website Design.

See case study for more information

Website: https://www.chrishaundaleeperez.com/

DTLA Cap Logo Design - Freelance Graphic Designer

August 2024

- Designed a custom logo for a small business, incorporating brand identity.
- Delivered multiple design concepts and refined based on client feedback.
- Provided final logo assets in various formats for web, and print.

See case study for more information

LINKS

Linkedin Page

https://www.linkedin.com/in/joel-reyes-ca1776/

Portfolio Link

joelreyes.xyz